-Huh? -The doors are closing.
-뭐? -문이 닫힙니다.
YOO SE-AH
유세아
A transfer student?
편입생?
Must be a bully.
깡패 여야합니다.
No, my mom told me about her.
아니, 엄마가 나한테 그 얘기를 했어.
Her parents took their own lives, so she's on her own.
그녀의 부모는 스스로 목숨을 끊었고, 그래서 그녀는 혼자입니다.
-Really?
-정말?
That's insane.
그건 미친 짓이야.
What? That's creepy.
무엇? 정말 소름끼친다.
Maybe she's got stuff going on too.
어쩌면 그녀에게도 무슨 일이 있을지도 모릅니다.
There's even a rumor she killed her parents.
소문도 나네요 그녀는 부모님을 죽였습니다.
A three-time national champion
3차례 전국 챔피언
and a next-generation Olympic prospect, Yoo Se-ah.
차세대 올림픽 유망주, 유세아.
-Be quiet. -I'm on the track team too.
- 조용히 하세요. -저도 육상팀에 속해 있어요.
-I also do the long jump. -I said be quiet.
-나도 멀리뛰기를 한다. - 조용히 하라고 했어요.
-Hey, she said be quiet! -Ouch.
-야, 조용히 하라고 했어! -아야.
Come on, these are a track athlete's legs.
자, 육상선수의 다리입니다.
They're basically still
그들은 기본적으로 여전히
elementary students up here, so they're inconsiderate.
여기 초등학생들, 그래서 그들은 배려가 없습니다.
If anyone bothers you again, just let me know.
누가 또 괴롭히면 그냥 알려주세요.
If you need to copy someone's homework, ask him, not me.
누군가의 숙제를 복사해야 한다면, 내가 아니라 그 사람에게 물어보세요.
You should do your own homework.
당신은 스스로 숙제를 해야 합니다.
I'm Kang Ha-joon.
저는 강하준이에요.
Well, since you're new here, I'll help you out.
글쎄요, 당신은 여기 처음 왔으니까요. 내가 도와줄게.
I'll help you out with the track team.
트랙팀에서 도와드리겠습니다.
Just trust me.
그냥 나를 믿으세요.
Skul!
스컬!
Legendary.
전설적.
The legendary skeleton
전설적인 해골
who never left the Demon King's side to the very end!
마왕의 곁을 떠나지 않은 사람 끝까지!
He's my minion, but you can have him.
그는 내 하수인이지만 당신이 그를 가질 수 있습니다.
He and I will protect you from all evil schemes.
그와 내가 당신을 보호할 것이다 모든 악한 계략에서
Hyeong-wook, put the knife down. Okay?
형욱아, 칼 내려놔. 좋아요?
Please calm down.
진정하세요.
No!
아니요!
No, Hyeong-wook!
안돼 형욱아!
Hyeong-wook!
형욱!
Get back in!
다시 들어가세요!
Hey! Close the door!
여기요! 문을 닫으세요!
IF WISHES COULD KILL
소원이 사람을 죽일 수 있다면
9:08 a.m.
오전 9시 8분
Yeah, it's a suicide.
응, 자살이야.
This should suffice without any further statement.
이것으로 충분할 것입니다 더 이상의 설명 없이.
Okay.
좋아요.
Please handle this quickly for the sake of the other kids.
빨리 처리해주세요 다른 아이들을 위해서.
Ma'am.
부인.
I'm going to the gym locker room to change.
체육관 라커룸으로 갈 거예요 변경합니다.
HARD WORK ALWAYS PAYS OFF
열심히 일하면 항상 보상을 받습니다
Seriously, Choi Hyeong-wook.
진심 최형욱.
Yeah, keep ignoring me like that.
응, 계속 그렇게 무시해.
The weather's nice anyway.
그나저나 날씨가 좋네요.
I guess I'll just camp out right here in front of your place!
난 그냥 여기서 캠핑을 할 것 같아 네 집 바로 앞이야!
Hey!
여기요!
I'm really about to barge in!
정말 막 들어가려고 해요!
I know I bailed on your birthday party,
내가 네 생일 파티에 참석하지 않았다는 걸 알아,
but do you really have to go this far?
그런데 꼭 이렇게까지 가야만 합니까?
Is that why you're here? To argue about that?
그게 당신이 여기 있는 이유인가요? 그것에 대해 논쟁하려고?
Just take this.
그냥 가져가세요.
It's your birthday present, so take it.
생일 선물이니까 받아가세요.
I'm giving you one early since I'm the only one who can't make it.
미리 하나 드릴게요 왜냐하면 나는 그것을 할 수 없는 유일한 사람이기 때문이다.
You're the only one?
당신은 유일한 사람입니까?
I already know Geon-woo's not coming.
건우가 안 온다는 건 이미 알고 있어요.
What? Why wouldn't Geon-woo come?
무엇? 건우는 왜 안오나요?
Geon-woo and Ha-joon will come for sure.
건우와 하준은 꼭 올 것이다.
Na-ri will probably be there to see Geon-woo.
나리는 아마 거기 있을 거예요 건우를 만나러.
Come on. Just take it already.
어서 해봐요. 그냥 가져가세요.
Okay?
좋아요?
Here. I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
여기. 미안해요 나는 약속을 지키지 못했습니다.
I know it doesn't sound like it, but I came to apologize.
나는 그것이 그렇게 들리지 않는다는 것을 안다. 그런데 사과하러 왔어요.
I'll get going now.
이제 가겠습니다.
Se-ah.
세아.
Something…
뭔가…
really strange happened to me today.
오늘 정말 이상한 일이 일어났어요.
I talked to you on the phone today.
오늘 전화로 얘기했어요.
Well, technically,
음, 기술적으로는
I just heard you talking to the other guys.
방금 네 말을 들었어 다른 남자들한테 얘기하는 중.
But it wasn't you.
하지만 그건 당신이 아니었어요.
I'm sorry I misunderstood, Se-ah.
오해해서 미안해, 세아.
Se-ah!
세아!
Se-ah, are you okay?
세아, 괜찮아?
Oh God.
오 맙소사.
God, are you okay?
맙소사, 괜찮으세요?
Oh dear.
이런.
I'm sorry, Coach.
죄송해요, 코치님.
Why would you be sorry?
왜 미안하겠어요?
Try not to think about anything today. Just rest at home.
오늘은 아무 생각도 하지 마세요. 그냥 집에서 쉬세요.
I'll talk to your homeroom teacher.
담임 선생님께 얘기해 볼게요.
Training is canceled tomorrow. Just rest well at home.
내일 훈련이 취소됩니다. 그냥 집에서 푹 쉬세요.
Okay?
좋아요?
Okay.
좋아요.
Are you okay going alone? Do you want me to take you home?
혼자 가도 괜찮아? 내가 당신을 집에 데려다 줄까요?
I'm okay.
난 괜찮아.
I can go by myself.
나 혼자 갈 수 있어요.
Just rest. Don't worry about training.
그냥 쉬세요. 훈련에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오.
Please let Se-ah's training be canceled this weekend.
세아의 훈련을 취소해주세요 이번 주말.
It granted a perfect score. Canceling training should be easy.
만점을 부여했습니다. 훈련을 취소하는 것은 쉬워야 합니다.
OCTOBER 24, 2008 KIM GEON-WOO
2008년 10월 24일 김건우
Coach.
코치.
I'm honestly fine now.
지금은 솔직히 괜찮아요.
Please don't cancel training this weekend.
이번 주말 훈련을 취소하지 마십시오.
Hey, Se-ah. Are you okay?
안녕, 세아. 괜찮으세요?
GIRIGO
지리고
"Your wish has been granted."
"당신의 소원이 이루어졌습니다."
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Did the timer come up?
타이머가 나왔나요?
It didn't, right?
그렇지 않았죠?
Did your training really get canceled?
훈련이 정말 취소됐나요?
Did your wish
소원대로 됐어
come true?
실현되다?
Cancel the training!
훈련을 취소하세요!
Cancel! Training!
취소하세요! 훈련!
-Cancel the training. -Please grant Geon-woo's wish.
-교육을 취소합니다. -건우의 소원을 들어주세요.
I'll disconnect it from the network and reset it.
네트워크 연결을 끊겠습니다 그리고 재설정하세요.
DELETE ALL
모두 삭제
POWERING OFF…
전원이 꺼지는 중...
-When did your training get canceled? -11:26.
-훈련이 언제 취소됐나요? -11:26.
That's way too specific.
너무 구체적이군요.
When the coach said training was canceled,
코치가 훈련이 취소되었다고 말했을 때
I checked my phone for the time.
나는 휴대폰으로 시간을 확인했다.
That's when you got the message?
그때 메시지를 받았나요?
-Yeah. -Maybe it's hacked.
-응. -해킹되었을 수도 있습니다.
Possibly.
혹시.
Look.
바라보다.
I'm telling you, this isn't a hack.
내가 말하는데, 이건 해킹이 아니다.
Can a hack kill someone?
해킹으로 사람을 죽일 수 있나요?
Hey, can an app kill someone, then?
그렇다면 앱이 사람을 죽일 수 있나요?
A lame app that grants your wishes?
소원을 들어주는 형편없는 앱?
It makes you kill yourself when the timer hits zero?
그것은 당신을 자살하게 만든다. 타이머가 0에 도달하면?
Do you seriously think that's real?
진지하게 그게 진짜라고 생각하시나요?
The timer appeared after their wishes were granted.
타이머가 나타났다 그들의 소원이 이루어진 후.
You all know what happened
무슨 일이 일어났는지 다들 아시죠
when Hyeong-wook's timer hit zero.
형욱의 타이머가 0이 되었을 때.
Oh, I see.
알겠어요.
You saw it, so we're just supposed to believe you?
당신은 그것을 보았다, 그럼 우리는 당신을 믿어야 하는 건가요?
The issue isn't that you saw it, but that only you did.
문제는 당신이 그것을 봤다는 것이 아니라, 하지만 그건 당신만이 한 일이에요.
Are you saying
Are you saying
I'm lying right now?
말하는 거야?
-Who knows? -"Who knows?" Fuck! Our friend died today!
나 지금 거짓말하고 있는 거야?
That's exactly what I'm trying to say!
- 누가 알겠어요? -"누가 알겠어요?" 못쓰게 만들다! 오늘 우리 친구가 죽었어!
-Guys, stop it. Okay? -Hey!
내가 말하려는 것이 바로 그것이다!
You're not his only friend!
- 얘들아, 그만해. 좋아요? -여기요!
We were already friends long before you moved here.
당신은 그의 유일한 친구가 아닙니다!
What, is the app possessed by a ghost?
우리는 이미 친구였습니다 당신이 여기로 이사오기 오래 전에요.
No, maybe you're the one who's possessed.
뭐야, 유령이 씌인 앱이야?
Just stop it now!
아니, 아마도 당신은 빙의된 사람일지도 모릅니다.
Geon-woo, why do you only cut me off?
이제 그만하세요!
Did I say anything wrong? She keeps talking creepy crap!
건우 씨, 왜 나만 잘라요?
Na-ri, I didn't mean to. It's just…
내가 뭔가 잘못 말했나요? 그녀는 계속 소름 끼치는 말을하고 있습니다!
I just hate it.
나리, 그럴 생각은 아니었어요. 그냥...
I see my dead mom and dad, injured so badly I can't recognize them…
난 그냥 싫어.
in my dreams every night.
돌아가신 엄마, 아빠가 보이네요. 너무 심하게 다쳐서 알아볼 수가 없어요…
Se-ah.
매일 밤 꿈에서.
And…
세아.
today, right in front of me,
그리고…
my friend died.
오늘, 내 바로 앞에서
I never want to see anyone close to me die again.
내 친구가 죽었어.
Not Geon-woo,
절대 보고 싶지 않아 나와 가까운 사람이 또 죽는다.
not you, not Ha-joon.
건우 아님,
Why would we die? That's bullshit.
너도 아니고 하준도 아니고.
GIRIGO
우리는 왜 죽을까요? 그건 헛소리야.
Whatever it is, it's no ordinary app.
지리고
It won't delete, even after a reset.
그것이 무엇이든, 그것은 평범한 앱이 아닙니다.
This won't stop either.
재설정 후에도 삭제되지 않습니다.
Can't we just break the phone?
이것도 멈추지 않을 것이다.
We can't. Breaking the phone won't get rid of the app.
그냥 전화 끊으면 안 돼요?
We should take a closer look at this app.
우리는 할 수 없습니다. 전화를 끊는다 앱을 제거하지 않습니다.
I'll grab my laptop from home. Then we'll find out.
우리는 이 앱을 좀 더 자세히 살펴봐야 합니다.
Then let's get everything we need and meet at my place.
집에서 노트북을 가져올게요. 그럼 알아보겠습니다.
Na-ri.
그럼 필요한 건 다 가져오자 그리고 내 집에서 만나요.
You're coming too, right?
나리.
Yeah.
너도 올 거야, 그렇지?
About what you said earlier,
응.
that you're having nightmares every night,
이전에 말씀하신 내용에 대해
I didn't know you were still struggling like that.
넌 매일 밤 악몽을 꾼단 말야
I'm sorry.
나는 몰랐다 당신은 아직도 그렇게 힘들어하고 있었군요.
When I transferred here,
죄송합니다.
I was going to quit the track team.
내가 여기로 전근했을 때,
But do you know why I didn't?
나는 육상팀을 그만두려고 했어요.
Thump.
그런데 내가 왜 그러지 않았는지 아세요?
When I was alone at my aunt's place,
딸꾹질.
I was so scared and miserable.
이모 댁에 혼자 있었을 때,
But this kid upstairs kept running around so loudly.
나는 너무 무서웠고 비참했습니다.
Whenever he saw me at school,
그런데 위층에 있는 이 아이는 계속 시끄럽게 뛰어다녔어요.
he'd go, "Hey, long jump gold medalist!"
그가 학교에서 나를 볼 때마다
He'd just go off like that.
그는 "야, 멀리뛰기 금메달리스트!"라고 말하곤 했습니다.
So
그는 그냥 그렇게 떠날 것입니다.
I thought,
그럼
"With him around, I won't be scared even if I'm alone."
내 생각엔
Thank you, Geon-woo.
"그 사람이 옆에 있으면 혼자 있어도 무섭지 않을 것 같아요."
Se-ah.
고마워요 건우님.
Do you want me to stay with you?
세아.
You don't have to.
내가 당신과 함께 있기를 원하시나요?
We all had a hard time.
그럴 필요는 없습니다.
Rest up first and come later.
우리 모두는 힘든 시간을 보냈습니다.
Okay.
먼저 쉬고 나중에 오세요.
SE-AH
좋아요.
Hey, Se-ah.
세아
Hello?
안녕, 세아.
Wasn't that fricking hilarious?
안녕하세요?
"Guys, stop it. Just stop it now."
그거 정말 웃기지 않았나요?
-That's crazy! -It's hilarious when that idiot does that.
"얘들아, 그만해. 이제 그만해."
But Se-ah's alone.
-말도 안돼! -저 바보가 그런 짓을 하면 정말 재미있어요.
Who the fuck does he think he is?
그런데 세아는 혼자예요.
What do you even see in that idiot to go out with him?
그 사람은 자신이 누구라고 생각하는 걸까요?
-You want him? -Fuck. I'm gonna kill you.
저 바보에게서 뭘 본 걸까요 그 사람과 데이트하려고?
I don't want that loser.
-그 사람을 원하시나요? -젠장. 난 널 죽일 거야.
How long do you think that idiot will hold out?
나는 그 패자를 원하지 않습니다.
I think he'll be joining Choi Hyeong-wook before sundown.
얼마나 걸릴 것 같나요 그 바보가 버틸 수 있을까?
-Why are you already-- -Quiet.
최형욱 합류할 것 같아요 해가 지기 전.
Listen.
-왜 벌써-- -조용해요.
Damn it. It hung up.
듣다.
Maybe my phone's hacked.
젠장. 전화가 끊겼어요.
They knew everything we said earlier.
내 휴대전화가 해킹당했을 수도 있습니다.
-Hacked? -Yeah.
그들은 우리가 앞서 말한 모든 것을 알고 있었습니다.
So…
-해킹됐나요? -응.
so the voice sounded just like yours.
그럼…
But it wasn't you. There's no way you'd talk like that.
그래서 목소리가 꼭 당신 목소리 같았어요.
What's wrong?
하지만 그건 당신이 아니었어요. 그런 식으로 얘기할 리가 없어요.
Hyeong-wook said the same thing.
무슨 일이야?
He said he heard my voice.
형욱도 같은 말을 했다.
I'll move the system apps and the Girigo files to my laptop
그는 내 목소리를 들었다고 말했습니다.
and see what they are.
시스템 앱을 옮길게요 그리고 Girigo 파일을 내 노트북에 저장해
I can do a factory reset on the phone to wipe it clean.
그리고 그것이 무엇인지 알아보세요.
What is it? Something's not working?
휴대전화로 공장 초기화를 할 수 있어요 깨끗하게 닦으려고.
No. It's weird because it's way too easy.
그것은 무엇입니까? 뭔가 작동하지 않나요?
The code's nothing special. How is it acting like a system app?
아뇨. 너무 쉽기 때문에 이상해요.
What about the timer?
타이머는 어떻습니까?
We can stop and delete the timer now, right?
중지하고 삭제할 수 있습니다. 지금 타이머 맞죠?
Yeah.
응.
It will take a few minutes.
몇 분 정도 걸립니다.
Is it really over now?
이제 정말 끝난 걸까요?
Yeah.
응.
Geon-woo, what's wrong?
건우 씨, 무슨 일이에요?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
I think I've got something in my eye.
내 눈에 뭔가 들어간 것 같아요.
Geon-woo, stop doing that. Just go rinse--
건우야, 그만 좀 해라. 가서 헹구세요--
Geon-woo.
건우.
Hey…
안녕...
Stay back.
물러서세요.
Geon-woo.
건우.
Don't do that.
그러지 마세요.
Don't do that. Don't…
그러지 마세요. 하지 마세요...
Geon-woo!
건우!
Guys, get out.
여러분, 나가세요.
All of you, out!
여러분, 나가세요!
I'll get the first aid kit.
구급상자 가져올게요.
Hey, Geon-woo.
안녕, 건우.
Geon-woo!
건우!
Se-ah, 119! Se-ah, call 119!
세아, 119! 세아, 119에 전화해!
Se-ah, now! Se-ah!
세아, 지금! 세아!
Hello, this is Building 323 in Gwangdong Village.
안녕하세요 323빌딩입니다 광동마을에서.
Apartment 608. Please send an ambulance now!
아파트 608. 지금 당장 구급차를 보내주세요!
Geon-woo.
건우.
It won't stop bleeding!
출혈이 멈추지 않습니다!
Hurry! Send an ambulance!
서두르다! 구급차를 보내세요!
REBOOTING DEVICE…
기기 재부팅 중...
Geon-woo.
건우.
Don't hang up, and keep talking, okay?
전화 끊지 말고 계속 얘기해, 알았지?
Ma'am!
부인!
Please send the police too…
경찰도 보내주세요…
Goddamn it!
젠장!
No!
아니요!
You're the reason you're all dying, you fucker.
당신이 이유예요 너 다 죽어가고 있어, 이 새끼야.
You screwed things up, you nobody.
당신이 일을 망쳤어요, 당신은 아무도 아니에요.
Now every single one of you will die here.
이제 너희 모두는 여기서 죽을 것이다.
"I can't breathe."
"숨을 쉴 수가 없어요."
"Oh, I can't breathe."
"아, 숨이 안 쉬어지는데."
SEORIN HOSPITAL
서린병원
Yoo Se-ah.
유세아.
You're really not going to tell me what happened?
너 진짜 나한테 말 안 할 거야 무슨 일이 있었나요?
How's Geon-woo?
건우는 어때요?
He's in the ICU.
그는 중환자실에 있어요.
But it's not just the injuries keeping him from waking up.
하지만 부상만 있는 게 아니다. 그가 깨어나지 못하게 막는다.
If it's not because of me, then why can't he wake up?
나 때문이 아니라면, 그럼 그 사람은 왜 깨어나지 못하는 걸까요?
I'm taking special care of Geon-woo,
건우를 특별히 돌보고 있어요
so he'll get better soon.
그러면 그 사람은 곧 나을 거예요.
Don't worry about him.
그 사람에 대해서는 걱정하지 마세요.
Focus on yourself first.
먼저 자신에게 집중하세요.
Geon-woo's folks were looking for you like crazy,
건우네 사람들 미친 듯이 당신을 찾고 있었어요
not knowing you kept him from killing someone.
당신이 그 사람을 지켜준 줄도 모르고 누군가를 죽이는 것으로부터.
Do you need anything?
필요한 것이 있나요?
Let me know. I can bring it from your home.
알려줘요. 집에서 가져올 수 있어요.
I'm okay.
난 괜찮아.
My aunt brought everything I needed earlier.
이모님이 가져오셨어요 이전에 필요한 모든 것.
But what about you?
하지만 당신은 어떻습니까?
Isn't your bag at my place?
당신 가방은 내 집에 없나요?
I can get it later.
나중에 받을 수 있어요.
The passcode is my birthday, so just drop by and grab it.
비밀번호는 내 생일이고, 그러니 그냥 들러서 가져가세요.
Do you know what I was thinking when I woke up this morning?
내가 무슨 생각을 했는지 아세요? 오늘 아침에 일어났을 때?
"I'm screwed."
"나 망했어."
"I'm gonna be late."
"늦을 것 같아요."
That was my biggest worry just this morning.
그게 가장 큰 걱정이었는데 바로 오늘 아침입니다.
Yeah.
응.
How did things end up like this?
어쩌다가 일이 이렇게 됐지?
KANG HA-YOUNG
강하영
-Hello? -Stop what you're doing!
-안녕하세요? -하던 일을 멈추세요!
Don't touch that thing in front of you.
앞에 있는 것을 만지지 마세요.
-What? -You guys messed with it today.
-무엇? -오늘은 너희들이 망쳤어.
That's why your friend went berserk.
그래서 당신의 친구가 광분한 것입니다.
You guys provoked the spirit.
당신들이 정신을 자극했습니다.
You almost died today.
당신은 오늘 거의 죽을 뻔했습니다.
Whether you believe it or not, you only survived thanks to that girl.
믿거나 말거나 당신은 그 소녀 덕분에 살아남았습니다.
How do you even know that?
그걸 어떻게 알죠?
Do you know what you messed with today?
오늘 네가 무슨 짓을 했는지 알아?
What?
무엇?
Jugu.
주구.
It's a conduit that spreads curses.
저주를 퍼뜨리는 통로입니다.
A smartphone app spreads curses?
스마트폰 앱이 저주를 퍼뜨린다?
Jugu doesn't have a fixed form.
주구에는 정해진 형식이 없습니다.
It can be a letter, a drawing, a photo, or a video.
그것은 편지일 수도 있고, 그림일 수도 있고, 사진이든, 영상이든.
If it can carry someone's thoughts,
누군가의 생각을 전달할 수 있다면
it can be used to spread curses.
저주를 퍼뜨리는 데 사용될 수 있습니다.
Ha-joon, come to me. I need to see you in person to help you.
하준아, 나에게로 와라. 당신을 직접 만나서 도와줘야 해요.
You kicked me out last time I went. Now you want me to go back?
지난번에 내가 갔을 때 당신이 나를 쫓아냈어요. 이제 내가 돌아가길 바라나요?
Kang Ha-joon, where is she?
강하준, 그녀는 어디에 있나요?
The girl who helped you.
당신을 도와준 소녀.
Se-ah?
세아?
HA-JOON
하준
Check the heart rhythm.
심장 박동을 확인하세요.
He's in asystole!
그는 수축기 상태입니다!
Administering epinephrine!
에피네프린을 투여하세요!
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
Please, no!
제발, 안돼!
You have to think of Se-ah! Please!
세아를 생각해야 해! 제발!
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
GIRIGO DO YOU WANT TO INSTALL THIS APP?
지리고 이 앱을 설치하시겠습니까?
INSTALLING…
설치 중...
Bangwool, take out your knife.
방울아, 칼을 꺼내라.
One.
하나.
Write down your name and birthdate on the paper.
이름과 생년월일을 적어주세요 종이에.
Two.
두 개.
Hold up the paper with your saju and name on it,
종이를 들어 올리세요 당신의 사주와 이름을 적고
and open the Girigo app.
그리고 Girigo 앱을 엽니다.
Three.
3.
Hit the record button,
녹화 버튼을 누르세요.
and make a wish.
소원을 빌어보세요.
Four.
4.
Make sure…
꼭…
SEND WISH
소원 보내기
…to hit the send button.
…보내기 버튼을 누르세요.
SENDING WISH…
소원을 보내는 중...
Yoo Se-ah!
유세아!
Did I do it right, Hyeong-wook?
형욱씨 제가 제대로 한 건가요?
Did you just make a wish?
방금 소원을 빌었나요?
Are you crazy?
제정신이에요?
People close to me are dying again,
나와 가까운 사람들이 또 죽어가고 있어요
and I can't handle it.
그리고 나는 그것을 처리할 수 없습니다.
But you're okay with your own death?
하지만 당신은 자신의 죽음에 대해 괜찮나요?
You believe in stuff like this?
당신은 이런 것들을 믿나요?
I thought you hated this stuff.
나는 당신이 이런 것을 싫어한다고 생각했습니다.
Se-ah.
세아.
There was something else besides us
우리 말고도 다른 게 있었어
at school that day.
그날 학교에서.
I said fucking get lost!
내가 말했잖아, 꺼져라!
Hey…
안녕...
And it was at my place too.
그리고 그것은 내 집에도 있었습니다.
Only those whose wish was granted can see it.
소원을 들어준 사람만 그것을 볼 수 있습니다.
I need to see what it is. That way…
나는 그것이 무엇인지 확인해야합니다. 그렇게 하면...
I can know what they're dealing with and find the solution.
나는 그들이 무엇을 다루고 있는지 알 수 있습니다 그리고 해결책을 찾으세요.
WISH GRANTED
소원이 이루어졌네요
Five.
다섯.
The timer
타이머
does not stop.
멈추지 않습니다.
Doctor! He is breathing on his own!
의사! 그는 스스로 숨을 쉬고 있습니다!
And the last one Hyeong-wook didn't know about.
그리고 마지막 형욱이는 몰랐어요.
When the timer hits zero…
타이머가 0에 도달하면…
Let Geon-woo return to exactly the way he used to be.
건우를 돌려보내라 정확히 그 사람이 그랬던 것처럼.
That's my wish.
그게 내 소원이야.
…you die.
…너는 죽는다.
Eight hours apart.
8시간 간격.
Did the timer
타이머를 켰어
stop?
그만해?
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang
자막 번역: 장성인